<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
     xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
     xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
     xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FreePromptHub - Latest AI Prompts</title>
    <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com</link>
    <description>Get the latest AI prompts for ChatGPT, Claude, and other AI tools. Free, tested prompts that actually work.</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2025 FreePromptHub</copyright>
    <managingEditor>contact@freeprompthub.com (FreePromptHub Team)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>contact@freeprompthub.com (FreePromptHub Team)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 15:08:14 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>FreePromptHub RSS Generator 1.0</generator>
    <atom:link href="https://www.freeprompthub.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <image>
      <url>https://www.freeprompthub.com/images/logo.png</url>
      <title>FreePromptHub - Latest AI Prompts</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>Write the Perfect Wedding Toast | Free AI Prompt</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/wedding-toast</link>
      <description>Write a wedding toast that&apos;s heartfelt, funny, and memorable - without embarrassing anyone or getting too drunk to deliver it.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Being asked to give a wedding toast is an honor - and terrifying. You want to be funny but not offensive, heartfelt but not sappy, memorable but not infamous. This prompt helps you craft a toast that hits all the right notes without mentioning exes, drunk stories, or that Vegas incident.]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/wedding-toast</guid>
      <category>Relationships</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Date Ideas That Actually Work | Free AI Prompt</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/first-date-ideas</link>
      <description>Plan first dates that don&apos;t suck. Fun, low-pressure ideas that lead to real conversation and second dates, not awkward silences.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dinner and a movie? Boring. Coffee? Job interview vibes. Netflix and chill? Way too presumptuous. This prompt helps you plan first dates that are actually fun, encourage real conversation, and give you both an easy out if there's no chemistry. No more awkward silences over overpriced pasta.]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/first-date-ideas</guid>
      <category>Relationships</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set Boundaries Without Feeling Guilty | Free AI Prompt</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/set-boundaries</link>
      <description>Set healthy boundaries without guilt. Learn to say no, protect your energy, and stop being a doormat while keeping relationships intact.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Tired of being everyone's doormat? Saying yes when you mean no? Feeling guilty for having needs? This prompt helps you set clear boundaries that protect your energy while maintaining relationships. No more resentment, no more burnout, no more being taken advantage of.]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/set-boundaries</guid>
      <category>Relationships</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deal with Toxic Friends | Free AI Prompt</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/toxic-friend</link>
      <description>Deal with toxic friends who drain your energy. Know when to fix it, when to step back, and when to end the friendship for good.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[That friend who only calls when they need something? Who makes everything about them? Who leaves you feeling exhausted after every interaction? Yeah, them. This prompt helps you identify toxic patterns, set boundaries, and decide whether to fix the friendship or end it.]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/toxic-friend</guid>
      <category>Relationships</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Fight Fair in Relationships | Free AI Prompt</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/couple-arguments</link>
      <description>Fight fair in relationships. Learn to resolve conflicts without damaging your bond, saying things you can&apos;t take back, or letting resentment build.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Every couple fights. The difference between couples who last and couples who don't isn't whether they argue - it's HOW they argue. This prompt helps you navigate conflicts without going nuclear, bringing up past sins, or saying things that leave permanent scars.]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/couple-arguments</guid>
      <category>Relationships</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dating App Messages That Get Responses | Free AI Prompt</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/dating-app-messages</link>
      <description>Write dating app messages that actually get responses. Stop sending &apos;hey&apos; and start real conversations that lead to dates.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA["Hey" gets ignored. "You're beautiful" is creepy. Pickup lines are cringe. So what DO you say? This prompt helps you write opening messages that stand out, start real conversations, and actually lead to dates. Works for Tinder, Bumble, Hinge, or any dating app.]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/dating-app-messages</guid>
      <category>Relationships</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handle Family Drama Like a Pro | Free AI Prompt</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/family-drama</link>
      <description>Navigate family drama without losing your mind. Scripts for holidays, politics, money talks, and dealing with difficult relatives.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Ah, family. Can't live with them, can't change your DNA. Whether it's your racist uncle at Thanksgiving, your mom's passive-aggressive comments about your life choices, or siblings fighting over money, this prompt helps you navigate family chaos while keeping your sanity intact.]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/family-drama</guid>
      <category>Relationships</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Write a Sincere Apology That Actually Works | Free AI Prompt</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/apology-sincere</link>
      <description>Write a genuine apology that actually repairs relationships. Get the exact words to fix your mistake and rebuild trust.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[You messed up. Maybe you said something hurtful, broke a promise, or let someone down. Now you need to apologize - but "sorry" isn't enough. This prompt helps you craft a genuine apology that takes full responsibility, shows you understand the impact, and demonstrates real change.]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/apology-sincere</guid>
      <category>Relationships</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Someone Out Without Being Weird | Free AI Prompt</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/ask-someone-out</link>
      <description>Ask someone out with confidence. Get the exact words to express interest respectfully, handle any response gracefully, and avoid being creepy.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[That person you like? Time to actually do something about it. But "hey, wanna hang out sometime?" isn't going to cut it. This prompt helps you express interest confidently, suggest something specific, and handle any response with grace. No pickup lines, no games, just genuine connection.]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/ask-someone-out</guid>
      <category>Relationships</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Break Up Respectfully | Free AI Prompt</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/break-up-kindly</link>
      <description>End a relationship with kindness and clarity. Get the exact words to break up respectfully without giving false hope or being cruel.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Breaking up sucks. There's no way around that. But HOW you do it matters - for them, for you, and for your future peace of mind. This prompt helps you find words that are clear, kind, and final. No mixed signals, no false hope, no unnecessary cruelty.]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/relationships/break-up-kindly</guid>
      <category>Relationships</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cut Grocery Bills in Half - Money | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/save-groceries</link>
      <description>AI prompt to cut grocery bills in half without eating ramen every night. Get practical money-saving strategies that actually work for real families.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Stop hemorrhaging money at the grocery store! This prompt creates a realistic grocery budget and shopping strategy that cuts your bills in half without living on pasta and beans. Perfect for families tired of choosing between eating well and saving money.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/save-groceries</guid>
      <category>Money &amp; Finance</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turn Clutter into $1000 - Money | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/sell-stuff</link>
      <description>AI prompt to turn household clutter into $1000+ cash. Get specific strategies for selling items you already own for maximum profit online and locally.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    That spare room isn't storage - it's a gold mine! This prompt helps you identify valuable items in your house and create a selling strategy to turn clutter into $1000+ cash. Perfect for decluttering while making serious money.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/sell-stuff</guid>
      <category>Money &amp; Finance</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make $500 Extra This Month - Money | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/side-income</link>
      <description>AI prompt to make an extra $500 this month with realistic side income ideas. No MLM schemes or get-rich-quick nonsense - just proven strategies that work.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Need extra cash fast? This prompt creates a realistic 30-day plan to earn $500+ using your existing skills and schedule. No MLM schemes, no risky investments - just proven side income strategies that work for busy adults.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/side-income</guid>
      <category>Money &amp; Finance</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emergency Fund Calculator Prompt - Money | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/emergency-fund</link>
      <description>Emergency Fund Calculator prompt that determines your ideal emergency savings amount and creates a personalized savings plan to achieve financial security.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Calculate exactly how much you need in your emergency fund based on your unique situation. Get a personalized savings plan that balances security with other financial goals.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/emergency-fund</guid>
      <category>Money &amp; Finance</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investment Portfolio Analyzer Prompt - Money | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/investment-analyzer</link>
      <description>Investment Portfolio Analyzer prompt that evaluates your investments, identifies risks, and provides rebalancing recommendations for optimal returns.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Get professional-grade portfolio analysis with this comprehensive investment prompt. Discover hidden risks, optimize asset allocation, and receive personalized rebalancing recommendations based on your goals and risk tolerance.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/investment-analyzer</guid>
      <category>Money &amp; Finance</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lower Your Monthly Bills - Money | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/negotiate-bills</link>
      <description>AI prompt to lower your monthly bills without switching services. Get negotiation scripts that actually work to reduce cable, phone, insurance, and more.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Stop overpaying for everything! This prompt creates specific negotiation scripts and strategies to cut your monthly bills by 20-50% without switching services or sacrificing quality. Perfect for people who hate confrontation but need to save money.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/negotiate-bills</guid>
      <category>Money &amp; Finance</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Budget Optimizer Prompt - Money | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/budget-optimizer</link>
      <description>AI Budget Optimizer prompt that analyzes your income and expenses to find hidden savings and create a personalized budget plan.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Transform your finances with this comprehensive budget analysis prompt. It identifies waste, finds hidden savings opportunities, and creates a personalized budget that actually works for your lifestyle.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/budget-optimizer</guid>
      <category>Money &amp; Finance</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fix Credit Score in 90 Days - Money | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/credit-repair</link>
      <description>AI prompt to fix your credit score in 90 days without expensive repair services. Get proven strategies to dispute errors and improve your credit fast.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Tired of being denied loans or paying sky-high interest rates? This prompt creates a 90-day credit repair plan that actually works - no expensive services needed. Perfect for people who need better credit fast for a major purchase or financial goal.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/credit-repair</guid>
      <category>Money &amp; Finance</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debt Avalanche Calculator Prompt - Money | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/debt-payoff</link>
      <description>Debt Avalanche Calculator prompt that creates a personalized debt elimination strategy to save thousands in interest and become debt-free faster.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Eliminate debt strategically with this powerful prompt that creates a customized payoff plan. Compare avalanche vs. snowball methods, calculate interest savings, and get a month-by-month roadmap to becoming debt-free.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/money/debt-payoff</guid>
      <category>Money &amp; Finance</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5-Minute Stress Relief - Health | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/health/stress-relief</link>
      <description>AI prompt for instant stress relief techniques you can do anywhere. Get 5-minute solutions for overwhelming anxiety and daily stress.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Feeling overwhelmed? This prompt creates instant stress relief techniques you can use anywhere. Perfect for busy adults who need to calm down FAST - at work, in traffic, or when life gets too much.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/health/stress-relief</guid>
      <category>Health &amp; Wellness</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleep Better Tonight - Health | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/health/sleep-better</link>
      <description>AI prompt for better sleep without pills or gadgets. Get science-backed sleep solutions that work tonight for better rest and energy.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Stop tossing and turning! This prompt creates a personalized sleep improvement plan using proven techniques. No expensive gadgets or pills - just science-backed methods that help you fall asleep faster and wake up more rested.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/health/sleep-better</guid>
      <category>Health &amp; Wellness</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lose 10 Pounds Simply - Health | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/health/lose-weight-simple</link>
      <description>AI prompt for simple weight loss without dieting. Get a sustainable plan to lose 10 pounds with realistic changes that fit your busy life.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Skip the complicated diets and expensive gym memberships. This prompt creates a realistic weight loss plan that works for busy adults who hate counting calories and doing workouts they can't pronounce. Sustainable changes that actually stick.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/health/lose-weight-simple</guid>
      <category>Health &amp; Wellness</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthy Meal Prep for Beginners - Health | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/health/meal-prep-beginner</link>
      <description>AI prompt for beginner meal prep that saves time and money. Get simple healthy meal prep plans that take 2 hours or less per week.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Stop spending $15 on "healthy" takeout every day! This prompt creates simple meal prep plans that save time and money. Perfect for beginners who want to eat better without spending all weekend in the kitchen.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/health/meal-prep-beginner</guid>
      <category>Health &amp; Wellness</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daily Mental Health Check-In - Health | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/health/mental-health</link>
      <description>AI prompt for daily mental health check-ins and wellness tracking. Simple tools to monitor and improve your mental well-being every day.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Take care of your mental health with simple daily check-ins. This prompt helps you track your mood, identify patterns, and build emotional resilience. Perfect for anyone who wants to prioritize their mental wellness.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/health/mental-health</guid>
      <category>Health &amp; Wellness</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Natural Energy Boost - Health | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/health/energy-boost</link>
      <description>AI prompt for natural energy boost without caffeine or energy drinks. Get sustainable energy solutions that last all day without crashes.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Tired of the coffee crash cycle? This prompt creates sustainable energy solutions that don't rely on caffeine or expensive supplements. Perfect for people who want consistent energy all day without the jitters or afternoon crashes.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/health/energy-boost</guid>
      <category>Health &amp; Wellness</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Habits That Stick - Health | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/health/habit-builder</link>
      <description>AI prompt for building healthy habits that actually stick. Get science-backed strategies to create lasting positive changes in your life.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Tired of starting healthy habits that fizzle out in a week? This prompt uses proven psychology to help you build lasting changes. Perfect for people who've tried and failed at habit building before.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/health/habit-builder</guid>
      <category>Health &amp; Wellness</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Fit at Home - Health | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/health/home-workout</link>
      <description>AI prompt for effective home workouts with no equipment needed. Get personalized fitness routines for beginners that actually work.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    No gym? No problem! This prompt creates personalized home workouts that actually work. Perfect for beginners or anyone who can't get to a gym regularly. Uses only your body weight and basic household items.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/health/home-workout</guid>
      <category>Health &amp; Wellness</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car Maintenance Planner - Everyday Prompt | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/car-maintenance</link>
      <description>Keep your car running without getting ripped off at the shop. Know what needs fixing and what can wait.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Save thousands on car repairs by knowing what really needs fixing and when. Stop shops from selling you stuff you don't need.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/car-maintenance</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clean &amp; Organize My Chaos - Everyday | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/clean-organize</link>
      <description>AI organizing prompt that turns your chaos into a clean, organized space. Step-by-step decluttering plan that actually works.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Turn your disaster zone into an organized, functional space. This prompt creates a realistic plan that doesn't require buying expensive organizers or dedicating your entire weekend. Perfect for ADHD brains, overwhelmed parents, or anyone who doesn't know where to start.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/clean-organize</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Difficult Conversation Script - Everyday | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/difficult-conversation</link>
      <description>AI script for handling difficult conversations with your boss, partner, family, or friends. Get the words, responses, and confidence you need.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Get the exact words for that conversation you've been avoiding. Whether it's asking for a raise, setting boundaries, or addressing conflict, this prompt gives you a script that sounds like you, not a robot.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/difficult-conversation</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Visit Prep Guide - Everyday Prompt | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/doctor-visit-prep</link>
      <description>Get the most from doctor visits. Know what to ask, what to bring, and how to get answers you need.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Stop wasting doctor visits. Get your health issues actually addressed with the right preparation and questions.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/doctor-visit-prep</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handle Bad Boss - Everyday Prompt | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/handle-bad-boss</link>
      <description>Survive a terrible boss without losing your mind or job. Protect yourself while looking for something better.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Deal with a toxic boss while protecting your sanity and career. Document everything and plan your exit strategy.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/handle-bad-boss</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Cheaper Insurance - Everyday Prompt | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/insurance-cheaper</link>
      <description>Cut your insurance costs by 30-50% without losing coverage. Know exactly what to say to get lower rates.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Stop overpaying for insurance. Get scripts to negotiate lower rates and find discounts you're missing.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/insurance-cheaper</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Meal Planner on a Budget - Everyday | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/meal-planner</link>
      <description>AI meal planning prompt that creates a week of meals, grocery list, and recipes based on your budget and dietary needs. Save time and money.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Stop stressing about "what's for dinner?" This prompt creates a complete week of meals, organized grocery list, and simple recipes that fit your budget and dietary needs. Perfect for busy families, singles, or anyone tired of eating the same things.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/meal-planner</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving Checklist Planner - Everyday Prompt | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/moving-checklist</link>
      <description>Move without losing your mind or stuff. Complete checklist and timeline for stress-free moving.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Don't forget anything when moving. Get a complete timeline and checklist customized for your situation.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/moving-checklist</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neighbor Complaint Handler - Everyday Prompt | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/neighbor-complaint</link>
      <description>Handle neighbor problems without starting a war. Get issues resolved while keeping the peace.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Resolve neighbor issues without making enemies. Get what you need while keeping things civil.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/neighbor-complaint</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resume That Gets Interviews - Everyday | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/resume-fixer</link>
      <description>AI resume writing prompt that transforms your experience into a resume that gets interviews. Beat ATS systems and impress hiring managers.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Transform your work experience into a powerful resume that beats ATS systems and gets you interviews. This prompt creates achievement-focused bullets, integrates keywords, and makes you sound impressive (but honest).
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/resume-fixer</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roommate Agreement Creator - Everyday Prompt | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/roommate-agreement</link>
      <description>Create roommate agreements that prevent drama. Set clear boundaries and expectations before problems start.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Avoid roommate drama with clear agreements upfront. Cover everything from dishes to guests before it becomes a fight.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/roommate-agreement</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Security Deposit Back - Everyday Prompt | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/security-deposit</link>
      <description>Get your security deposit back in full. Document everything and handle move-out like a pro.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Stop landlords from stealing your deposit. Create documentation that forces them to return your money.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/security-deposit</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Professional Sick Day Message - Everyday Prompt | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/sick-day-excuse</link>
      <description>Call in sick professionally when you need to. Craft believable messages that maintain your reputation.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Take a sick day without damaging your reputation. Send messages that sound professional and believable.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/sick-day-excuse</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Side Hustle Starter Pack - Everyday | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/side-hustle</link>
      <description>AI prompt to find side hustles you can start TODAY with what you already have. Make extra money fast without MLMs or scams.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Need extra money NOW? This prompt finds legitimate side hustles you can start today with the skills and stuff you already have. No MLMs, no "get rich quick" BS - just real ways to make money this week.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/side-hustle</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vacation Request That Gets Approved - Everyday Prompt | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/vacation-request</link>
      <description>Get your vacation request approved. Write requests that bosses say yes to, even during busy times.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Get your time off approved even when it's inconvenient. Frame your request so bosses have to say yes.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/vacation-request</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Fit in My Living Room - Everyday | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/workout-home</link>
      <description>AI home workout prompt that creates a personalized fitness plan. No gym needed - get fit in your living room with whatever equipment you have.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    No gym? No problem. This prompt creates a realistic workout plan you can do at home with whatever equipment you have (or don't have). Perfect for beginners, busy parents, or anyone who hates gyms.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/workout-home</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buy Used Car Smart - Everyday Prompt | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/buy-used-car</link>
      <description>Buy a used car without getting scammed. Know what to check, what to ask, and how to negotiate the best deal.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Don't get ripped off buying a used car. Get a complete inspection checklist and negotiation strategy.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/buy-used-car</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fix My Budget in 30 Days - Everyday | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/budget-emergency</link>
      <description>Emergency budget prompt for when money is tight. Get a 30-day survival plan, find hidden money, and create a path out of financial crisis.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    When you're drowning in bills and don't know what to pay first, this prompt creates an emergency budget plan. Find hidden money, prioritize bills, and build a realistic path to financial stability.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/budget-emergency</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Bio Creator Prompt - Content | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/content/social-bio</link>
      <description>Social Media Bio Creator - Write the perfect bio for Instagram, Twitter, LinkedIn, or TikTok. Stand out in 150 characters or less.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Stop struggling with that tiny bio box. Create bios that make people want to follow you, show your personality, and work perfectly for each platform's vibe.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/content/social-bio</guid>
      <category>Content Creation</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank You Note Generator Prompt - Content | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/content/thank-you-note</link>
      <description>Thank You Note Generator - Write heartfelt thank you messages for gifts, help, or kindness. Never struggle with what to say again.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Write perfect thank you notes that actually sound sincere. Whether it's for a gift, a favor, or job interview, express genuine gratitude without sounding generic or fake.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/content/thank-you-note</guid>
      <category>Content Creation</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube Script Generator Prompt - Content | FreePromptHub</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/content/youtube-script</link>
      <description>YouTube Script Generator prompt that creates viral video scripts with perfect hooks, high retention, and CTAs that drive views, subscribers, and engagement.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                    Create YouTube scripts that hook viewers instantly, maintain high retention, and drive explosive channel growth. Generate scripts optimized for the algorithm with perfect pacing, storytelling, and engagement triggers.
                ]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/content/youtube-script</guid>
      <category>Content Creation</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apartment Hunting Without Getting Scammed | Free AI Prompt</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/apartment-hunting</link>
      <description>Find an apartment without getting scammed. Know what to look for, what questions to ask, and red flags that mean run away fast.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Looking for an apartment sucks. Between scam listings, hidden fees, terrible landlords, and that weird smell they swear will go away, it's a minefield. This prompt helps you know exactly what to look for, what questions to ask, and when to run away - before you sign anything.]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/apartment-hunting</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Ask for a Raise (And Get It) | Free AI Prompt</title>
      <link>https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/ask-for-raise</link>
      <description>Ask for a raise and actually get it. Build your case, time it right, and negotiate like a pro without threatening to quit.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[You're underpaid and you know it. But asking for more money feels like defusing a bomb - one wrong move and your job explodes. This prompt helps you build an airtight case, pick the perfect timing, and negotiate like someone who knows their worth - without ultimatums or awkwardness.]]></content:encoded>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.freeprompthub.com/prompts/everyday/ask-for-raise</guid>
      <category>Everyday Life</category>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:58:04 GMT</pubDate>
      <dc:creator>FreePromptHub Team</dc:creator>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>